...two of which are fairly close to me.
(Raj:)Her spontaneity is contagious.
(Bernadette:)Who's Siri?
Is he dating somebody new?
(Howard:)Yes. His phone.
(Bernadette:)Is that cute or creepy?
(Howard:)Uh-huh.
(Raj:)Can I pour you some wine?
I think you'll enjoy it.
(Raj:)Traditional choice with Peking duck
is a sauvignon blanc...
(Raj:)...but Siri suggested an off-dry Riesling.
(Raj:)I wasn't sure...
...but I didn't wanna have an argument
with her in the middle of Trader Joe's.
(Raj:)Now, what should we put Siri in
for dinner?
Leopard, sparkles?
Or to paraphrase Coco Chanel:
"You can never go wrong
with a little black case."
(Raj:)Siri, play some smooth jazz.
(Siri:)Playing smooth jazz.